[
    {
        "question": "🧞‍♂️",
        "response": "جني"
    },
    {
        "question": "🧌",
        "response": "قزم"
    },
    {
        "question": "🧙",
        "response": "ساحر"
    },
    {
        "question": "🧑‍🏫",
        "response": "مدرس"
    },
    {
        "question": "🕵️",
        "response": "محقق"
    },
    {
        "question": "👾",
        "response": "لعبه"
    },
    {
        "question": "🫘",
        "response": "حبوب"
    },
    {
        "question": "🌽",
        "response": "ذره"
    },
    {
        "question": "🎃",
        "response": "يقتين"
    },
    {
        "question": "🇪🇬",
        "response": "مصر"
    },
    {
        "question": "🫀",
        "response": "قلب"
    },
    {
        "question": "👃",
        "response": "انف"
    },
    {
        "question": "👀",
        "response": "عيون"
    },
    {
        "question": "😷",
        "response": "مريض"
    },
    {
        "question": "👻",
        "response": "شبح"
    },
    {
        "question": "🤖",
        "response": "روبوت"
    },
    {
        "question": "♻️",
        "response": "اعاده"
    },
    {
        "question": "🖌️",
        "response": "قلم"
    },
    {
        "question": "🧂",
        "response": "ملح"
    },
    {
        "question": "🏴‍☠️",
        "response": "قراصنه"
    },
    {
        "question": "⚖️",
        "response": "عداله"
    },
    {
        "question": "🧲",
        "response": "مغنطيس"
    },
    {
        "question": "💬",
        "response": "كومنت"
    },
    {
        "question": "🔔",
        "response": "جرس"
    },
    {
        "question": "🖱️",
        "response": "فار"
    },
    {
        "question": "✂️",
        "response": "مقص"
    },
    {
        "question": "⛱️",
        "response": "شمسيه"
    },
    {
        "question": "🛸",
        "response": "مركبه فضائيه"
    },
    {
        "question": "🔒",
        "response": "قفل"
    },
    {
        "question": "🎧",
        "response": "سماعه"
    },
    {
        "question": "🗑️",
        "response": "سله"
    },
    {
        "question": "👑",
        "response": "تاج"
    },
    {
        "question": "✉️",
        "response": "ظرف"
    },
    {
        "question": "🧸",
        "response": "دميه"
    },
    {
        "question": "🗝️",
        "response": "مفتاح"
    },
    {
        "question": "🦚",
        "response": "طاوس"
    },
    {
        "question": "🐟",
        "response": "سمكه"
    },
    {
        "question": "⚰️",
        "response": "قبر"
    },
    {
        "question": "🦎",
        "response": "سحليه"
    },
    {
        "question": "🪜",
        "response": "سلم"
    },
    {
        "question": "💎",
        "response": "الماس"
    },
    {
        "question": "💿",
        "response": "اسطوانه"
    },
    {
        "question": "💡",
        "response": "لمبه"
    },
    {
        "question": "⌚",
        "response": "ساعه"
    },
    {
        "question": "🕋",
        "response": "كعبه"
    },
    {
        "question": "⛺",
        "response": "خيمه"
    },
    {
        "question": "🏠",
        "response": "منزل"
    },
    {
        "question": "🏔️",
        "response": "جبل"
    },
    {
        "question": "⛄",
        "response": "رجل ثلج"
    },
    {
       "question": "🌸",
        "response": "ورده"
    },
    {
       "question": "🐚",
        "response": "صدفه"
    },
    {
       "question": "🔥",
        "response": "نار"
    },
    {
       "question": "🐧",
        "response": "بطريق"
    },
    {
       "question": "🐶",
        "response": "كلب"
    },
    {
       "question": "☕",
        "response": "قهوه"
    },
    {
       "question": "⚡",
        "response": "برق"
    },
    {
       "question": "☁️",
        "response": "سحاب"
    },
    {
       "question": "✨",
        "response": "نجوم"
    },
    {
       "question": "🌋",
        "response": "بركان"
    },
    {
       "question": "✈️",
        "response": "طياره"
    },
    {
       "question": "🚀",
        "response": "صاروخ"
    },
    {
       "question": "💰",
        "response": "فلوس"
    },
    {
       "question": "🥚",
        "response": "بيضه"
    },
    {
       "question": "🗿",
        "response": "صنم"
    },
    {
       "question": "🐦",
        "response": "حمامه"
    },
    {
       "question": "🐤",
       "response": "كتكوت"
}
]
